What do we hear when we listen with our
[Music]
hearts? Is it the hopes of parents even
before they first lay eyes on their
[Music]
child? Is it the ambitions of a young
man taking his first career steps?
Or is it the plight of families whose
lives and livelihoods are swept
[Music]
away? Through the power of listening, we
understand different people and how we
can make a difference in their lives.
We hear our
customers and we're here to provide them
with financial freedom and peace of
mind through our comprehensive range of
products and solutions that cater to
their savings and protection needs.
[Music]
We hear our people and we're here to
support their aspirations through every
stage of their careers. From charting a
promising career path for our
employees to helping our salesforce
achieve their professional goals and
personal
fulfillment to forming strong strategic
alliances with our bank and affinity
partners through our innovative point of
sale tools. We also support our
salesforce in ensuring a customer
ccentric approach to everything we
do. We hear our
community and we're here to bring
comfort and
relief through every moment of
difficulty and uncertainty.
[Music]
Founded in the UK in 1848 and
established in Malaysia in
1924, our vision is to become the number
one insurer in the hearts and minds of
all
[Music]
Malaysians. We are Credential, always
listening, always understanding.